{
    "subject": "Cornel_West",
    "predicate": "isKnownFor",
    "object": "Race_Matters",
    "human_readable": "Cornel West is known for Race Matters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8750205039978027,
            "question": "What is Cornel West known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6769822239875793,
            "question": "Who is Cornel West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6543548107147217,
            "question": "How has Cornel West's work influenced discussions about race and social justice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6513859629631042,
            "question": "Can you name some of Cornel West's other notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5421704649925232,
            "question": "In what field is Cornel West influential?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5056853294372559,
            "question": "What does the title 'Race Matters' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4493802487850189,
            "question": "What impact has Cornel West's work had on society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4402492940425873,
            "question": "What are some of Cornel West's main areas of focus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3239685595035553,
            "question": "Why is Cornel West considered an important public intellectual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28428348898887634,
            "question": "What are some of the key arguments presented in 'Race Matters'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cornel West is known for Race Matters.",
            "html": "yago_31620_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Cornel West considered an important public intellectual?",
            "html": "yago_31620_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Cornel West's main areas of focus?",
            "html": "yago_31620_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has Cornel West's work had on society?",
            "html": "yago_31620_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31620_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents indeed supports that Cornel West is associated with the book \"Race Matters\", as mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31620/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which mention that Dr. Cornel West has authored several books, including \"Race Matters.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}